CURRICULUM VITAE

Personal Details



First and Family Name: Maria Pieroszkiewicz

Address: ul. Wieczorka 32, 43-190 Mikołów, Poland

Phone: +48693324767

E-mail: maria.pieroszkiewicz@gmail.com
GitHub: https://github.com/marypieroszkiewicz
LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/marypieroszkiewicz

Date of birth: 09.05.1985

■ Professional summary

Front-End Developer, Web Designer solid experience in designing website interfaces and developing advanced web applications. Talented individual with fresh look and desirable character traits shaped by many years of sport training. Endurance in achieving set goals, life-long learning attitude and need to share inborn creativity.

■ Education

10.2007 – 06.2011 Bachelor Degree (Information Technology)

The Katowice Institute of Information Technologies (Wyższa Szkoła

Technologii Informatycznych) Katowice, Poland

Majors: web design, multimedia and website development

09.2005 – 07.2007 Computer Technician Information Technology and Internet High

School (Szkoła Informatyki i Internetu), Gliwice, Poland

■ Further Training

02.2017 - 03.2017 Computer Become Front-End Developer (6-weeks course, certified);

Coders Lab, Katowice, Poland

12.2013 JavaScript Basics (2 days); Functionite, Warsaw, Poland

11.2013 Web Design Specialist (4-day course, certified);

Compendium Centrum Edukacyjne Spółka z o.o., Katowice, Poland

10.2013 Responsive Web Design for Front-End Developers (1 day);

DevMeetings, Cracow, Poland

10.2013 Myths and problems of Agile - Scrum myths (1 day);

CodeSprinters, Cracow, Poland

Professional experience

02.2015 - 04.2015

i-Systems

Junior Front-End Developer

Commmissioned e-commerce projects work on demand

04.2013 - 06.2013

Creative Agency Global Performance

Junior Front-End Developer / Web Designer

- Webpage maintenance and administration www.sunweb-oferty.pl
- Webpage maintenance and administration www.fitcare.ajdi.pl
- Graphic Design for festive sweater collection section

Since 02.2010

Web Designer/Web Developer (Freelance)

- Successfully completed 7 projects ensuring customer satisfaction
- Analyzed client's goals and requirements
- Developed conceptual designs for the websites
- Created graphics and cut layouts
- Coded HTML / CSS templates or using the content management system Joomla! / WordPress
- Provided websites administration support
- Ensured technical support and websites SEO

Clients:

- Biuro Usług Projektowych i Nadzoru Budowlanego "PROINBUD"
- Kancelaria Radcy Prawnego Anna Richter
- Compleo Terapie Naturalne
- "Geosolis" Pracownia Geologiczna Maciej Bałys
- "EnglishCom" Katarzyna Buch-Gasz

Additional experience

Since 06.2009

Front-End Developer / Web Designer / Service Administrator Śląski Klub Karate "GOLIAT", Katowice, Poland

 Designed, implemented and maintained club's website (500+ visitors per day)

I hereby agree for processing the following personal information strictly for the purposes of job recruitment in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act dated 29.08.1997 (uniform text: Journal of Laws of the Republic of Poland 2002 No 101, item 926 with further amendments) /s/ Maria Pieroszkiewicz

■ Skills

See the attachment

■ Language Skills

English: intermediate

Polish: native speaker

■ Interests

Professional: front-end development, web development, web design, graphic

design, ux/ui, reader of (front-end, web development blogs,

.net magaizne, web designer magazine), newest technologies, social media, participating in different industry conferences and events

Others: martial arts (Kung Fu and Karate – 3rd place in OYAMA TOP Puchar

Polski OYAMA PFK competition - semi-knockdown karate, 09.2009), skiing, spiritual growth, cooking in accordance with five elements theory, (dietetics in traditional chinese medicine), travelling, origami

References

References available upon request



First and Family Name: Maria Pieroszkiewicz

Address: ul. Wieczorka 32, 43-190 Mikołów, Poland

Phone: +48693324767

E-mail: maria.pieroszkiewicz@gmail.com
GitHub: https://github.com/marypieroszkiewicz
LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/marypieroszkiewicz

Date of birth: 09.05.1985

Programming: HTML, CSS, CMS (Wordpress / Joomla!), Responsive Web Design,

Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, Git, Gulp, PHP, MySQL

Tools: Sublime Text 3, GitHub

Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Flash,

InDesign, Premiere Pro)

Corel Draw, Autodesk 3ds Max (modeling, texturing, animation

basics)

Operations systems: Mac OS X

Windows 95/98/NT/2000/XP/2003/Vista/7/10

Linux: Ubuntu, Debian

Others: SEO/SEM basics

Computer hardware diagnostics and repair